<?xml version="1.0"?>
<learningObject editorVersion="3" targetFolder="Nottingham" name="Staying Safe Online" language="en-GB" navigation="Historic" textSize="12" theme="default" displayMode="fill window" responsive="true" stylesheet="FileLocation + 'media/BP-xhibit-stylesheetv2.css'" ic="FileLocation + 'media/BLETCHLEY_PARK_LOGO_RGB_NEG.png'" icTip="BP Logo" icPosition="right" styles="/* custom code for copyright position at bottom of last page */&#10;&#10;.page-wrap {&#10;  min-height: 100%;&#10;  /* equal to footer height */&#10;  margin-bottom: -100px; &#10;}&#10;.page-wrap:after {&#10;  content: &quot;&quot;;&#10;  display: block;&#10;}&#10;.site-footer, .page-wrap:after {&#10;  height: 100px; &#10;}&#10;.site-footer {&#10;  margin-top: 50px;&#10;  background: white;&#10;  position: absolute;&#10;  left: 10px;&#10;  right: 0;&#10;  bottom: 0;&#10;}&#10;&#10;&#10;&#10;" trackingMode="full_first" trackingPassed="80%" trackingPageTimeout="5" forceTrackingMode="false" category="Education"><connectorHotspotImage linkID="PG1504700671404" name="Welcome to Staying Safe" text="Explore the images on the right and then see how well you &amp;nbsp;  &lt;button class=&quot;ui-button ui-widget ui-corner-all&quot; href=&quot;#&quot; onclick=&quot;x_navigateToPage(false,{type:'linkID',ID:'PG1504702024932'}); return false;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; understand online safety&amp;nbsp;&lt;/button&gt;&#10;&#10;&#10;" textWidth="narrow" url="FileLocation + 'media/onlinesafety.jpg'" tip="Online safety topics" highlight="false" hicol="0xFFFF00" align="Left" notFoundMessage="could not be found in this project." continueBtnTxt="Close" unmarkForCompletion="true" home="true" back="true" next="false"><cHotspot linkID="PG1504700910802" name="Patch it!" destination="PG1504700756149" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="0" y="321" w="316" h="254"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1504701638274" name="Wifi" destination="PG1504701174800" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="0" y="0" w="292" h="301"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535097199100" name="Password" destination="PG1535097779057" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="585" y="81" w="310" h="140"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535099850323" name="Malware" destination="PG1535098859949" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="296" y="11" w="305" h="292"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535104107825" name="USB devices" destination="PG1535099728499" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="309" y="880" w="292" h="309"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535104183815" name="IOT Devices" destination="PG1535104270942" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="17" y="592" w="296" h="305"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535111112239" name="Mobile devices" destination="PG1535111047971" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="875" y="334" w="313" h="269"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535111759185" name="Social Media" destination="PG1535111833469" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="895" y="2" w="292" h="298"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535112572419" name="Personal information" destination="PG1535112619599" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="7" y="900" w="283" h="291"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535112790661" name="Online shopping" destination="PG1535112672749" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="605" y="911" w="288" h="278"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535114823595" name="Trolls" destination="PG1535114860579" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="385" y="319" w="434" h="561"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535115719324" name="Online games" destination="PG1535117702139" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="902" y="608" w="293" h="276"/><cHotspot linkID="PG1535115772495" name="Predator" destination="PG1535116326290" exitNav="all" text="Description for the hotspot" x="895" y="899" w="304" h="298"/></connectorHotspotImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535117702139" name="Online games" align="Left" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00572-game-2294201_640.jpg'" tip="gamer" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p>It&#39;s easy to forget that something fun can have some risks and cyber criminals are well aware when we are at our most vulnerable.</p>

<p>Perhaps there&#39;s a patch or cheat that you can use?&nbsp;Or a offer of cheap skins or other game gear. These are all great routes to get you to install <a href="#" onclick="x_navigateToPage(false,{type:'linkID',ID:'PG1535099728499'}); return false;">malware </a>on your computer.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Multi-player games are just as much a part of social media as Instagram but there are usually no barrier to chatting with people you&#39;ve never met in real life. You can&#39;t be sure who you&#39;re talking with so never use your real name or reveal personal information.</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535116326290" name="Online predators" align="Left" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00571-programmer-3607627_640.png'" tip="Enter a Description for Accessibility" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p><span style="color:#c0392b;"><strong>Do you consider the risks when posting photos?</strong></span>&nbsp;</p>

<p>This&nbsp;is what online predators look for in photos others post:</p>

<ul>
	<li>Is there enough room to &#39;superimpose&#39; another figure into the image?</li>
	<li>Are they in a state of undress (even with emoticons placed modestly - these can be removed and body parts can be digitally copied in).</li>
</ul>

<p><strong><span style="color:#c0392b;">Do you know who you&#39;re talking to?</span></strong></p>

<p>It is really easy to pretend to be someone other than you are on social media - that is one of the reasons it is popular. Don&#39;t agree to meet in real life without an adult to accompany you.</p>

<p><strong><span style="color:#c0392b;">Do you know why they are talking to you?</span></strong></p>

<p>Are they recruiting a friend or a victim? Be very careful of individuals expressing extreme views on any topic. Talk it out with someone you trust.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535114860579" name="When Trolls Attack" align="Right" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00569-forbidden-151987_1280.png'" tip="troll warning" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p><span style="color:#c0392b;"><strong>It&rsquo;s not your fault - it&#39;s the bully that&#39;s got the problem</strong></span></p>

<ul>
	<li>Keep the offending&nbsp;post/message (take a screenshot - but not in Snapchat*)</li>
	<li>Don&rsquo;t reply to the sender</li>
	<li>Block the offender and un-friend them</li>
	<li>Involve an adult - a parent, sibling, or someone you trust</li>
	<li>Report problems promptly to the social network or mobile phone operator</li>
	<li>For serious issues, you should involve the police - this includes inappropriate sexual suggestions, racist remarks, ongoing bullying or harassment</li>
</ul>

<p><strong><span style="color:#c0392b;">Trolls are not as anonymous as they think they are - it is always worth reporting a problem.</span></strong></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>* Snapchat will report to the troll that a screenshot has been taken. Take a picture of your screen with another camera.</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535112672749" name="Online shopping" align="Bottom" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00573-ecommerce-2140603_640.jpg'" tip="online shopping" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p>Online shopping is really convenient for cyber criminals - you can just give them your payment card details!</p>

<p>The green padlock symbol (and often the word <em>secure</em>)&nbsp; at the start of the web site&#39;s address will tell you that the connection between you and the site and is private so that a &#39;man in the middle&#39; cannot see the details you type.&nbsp;</p>

<p>This doesn&#39;t guarantee the site is safe though.&nbsp;Criminals can clone web sites that look exactly like real online stores so always be careful of links in emails directing you to today&#39;s special offer. But whenever you are asked for payment details it should always be there.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Never reveal personal information like PIN numbers or login details when ordering things - this could be a very bad sign!</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535112619599" name="Personal information" align="Right" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00570-data-1590455_640.jpg'" tip="fingerprint" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p><strong><span style="color:#c0392b;">What do you think personal information is?</span></strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Your phone number</li>
	<li>Where your parents work</li>
	<li>Where you go&nbsp;</li>
	<li>Where you live</li>
	<li>Your date of birth</li>
	<li>Your national insurance number</li>
	<li>Your bank details</li>
	<li>Passwords</li>
	<li>Where you used to live</li>
	<li>Who your friends are</li>
	<li>Your pet&#39;s name</li>
</ul>

<p>The list is almost endless and most of these are pieces of information you obviously wouldn&#39;t share publicly. But all these little pieces of information can be drawn from your &#39;digital footprint&#39; and&nbsp;used to: <strong>impersonate you; steal from you; manipulate you; hurt you!</strong></p>

<p>Be very careful who you reveal personal information and always ask <strong>why?</strong>&nbsp;when organisations ask for information that doesn&#39;t seem relevant, even if they appear to be legitimate.&nbsp;</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535111833469" name="Social media&amp;nbsp;" align="Left" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00568-twitter-292994_1920.jpg'" tip="social media apps" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p>Social media apps are a great way to stay in touch and share information, but you can share too much!</p>

<p>You need to be very&nbsp;aware of:</p>

<p><strong>Loss of control:</strong> Once you post it, it can&rsquo;t be taken back even if you regret it. You should think before you send anything, only post content you&rsquo;d be proud to put your name against!</p>

<p><strong>Trusting Peers:</strong> Beware of peer pressure and following the crowd, don&rsquo;t be pressured into oversharing just because there&rsquo;s an expectation of trust. Take care of yourself first and follow your gut when it comes to sharing personal details and content.</p>

<p><strong>Location information:</strong> Pictures and videos can share information about where you go, what you own and what you do. This can be very useful for a criminal.</p>

<p>It&#39;s essential that you check your <strong>privacy settings</strong>, as well as the terms and conditions for using an application - you may be giving your videos and pictures to someone to use however they wish.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535111047971" name="Mobile devices" align="Right" url="FileLocation + 'media/A00567-agreement-2548138_1920.jpg'" tip="laptop smartphone and tablet" imagesize="auto" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<p>Smart phones and tablets use is growing at 10 times that of PCs. We are using those devices in more locations to do more things. By the end of 2014 there were as many mobile devices as people on the planet.</p>

<p>As a result, they are more and more attactive to cyber criminals. So it is important to:</p>

<ul>
	<li>always set a passcode (or fingerprint/face recognition)</li>
	<li>logout of your accounts when they are not being used</li>
	<li>only download and install from trusted sources</li>
</ul>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></bleedingImage><bleedingImage linkID="PG1535104270942" name="The Internet of Things (IOT)" align="Left" url="FileLocation + 'media/networks-iot-cut.png'" tip="computer networks" imagesize="auto"><![CDATA[<p>The Internet of Things is eclipsing that of mobile and the number of connected devices is growing at an exponential rate. It is estimated that by 2020, there will be 26 billion connected devices*. The types of connected devices in the home range from smart TVs, home security systems and refrigerators to coffee machines. This volume of connected devices means that threats are also increasing.&nbsp;</p>

<p>If you have internet connected devices in your home, make sure that:</p>

<ul>
	<li>you register the device with the manufacturer and apply updates when prompted</li>
	<li>change any default administration password to a strong one of your own</li>
	<li>disconnect devices that are not in use</li>
	<li>cover web camera lenses when they are not in use</li>
	<li>avoid buying cheap devices without any form of security</li>
</ul>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>* <em>Source: Gartner.com</em></p>
]]></bleedingImage><textGraphics linkID="PG1535097779057" name="Passwords" align="Left" imagesize="auto" url="FileLocation + 'media/password-866977_960_720.jpg'" tip="passwords entry boxes" transcriptbuttonlabel="Transcript" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<h3>Love them or hate them, passwords are part of our daily life. But what makes a GOOD password?</h3>

<p>Simply speaking, it needs to be:</p>

<ul>
	<li>Hard for a hacker to guess</li>
	<li>Slow for a computer to attack by brute force</li>
	<li>Easy to remember</li>
	<li>Easy to associate with the site you are trying to access</li>
</ul>

<p>The strongest passwords use a mixture of letters, numbers and other characters.</p>

<p>Longer passwords - 12 characterts or more is better - can be remembered by using a phrase, song lyrics or a mental image.</p>

<p>To help you remember passwords for specific sites, add a letter or word that links your password to the site. The main part of your password can still be the same for several sites.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></textGraphics><text linkID="PG1504700756149" name="Apply the updates!" home="true" back="true" next="false"><![CDATA[<ul>
	<li>Install the security updates on your PC, Mac, Phone, router, smart TV, Webcam &hellip;. or at least make sure that automatic updates are not turned off.</li>
	<li>Using old hardware or operating systems (Windows XP) is risky</li>
	<li>Microsoft won&#39;t end security updates for your&nbsp;Windows 7&nbsp;PC until Jan. 14, 2020<img alt="" height="617" src="FileLocation + 'media/updates.jpg'" style="float:right" width="784" /></li>
</ul>
]]></text><tabNav linkID="PG1535098859949" name="Malware" text="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;anti-virus&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; src=&quot;FileLocation + 'media/virus-mcafee.png'&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;Malware&amp;#39; is short for &lt;strong&gt;malicious software&lt;/strong&gt; and can appear in a number of different forms such as&amp;nbsp;viruses, spyware,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;worms,&amp;nbsp;trojans,&amp;nbsp;rootkits and ransomware.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;They are all designed to steal something from you and are a source of a great deal of cyber crime. Sometimes what they steal isn&amp;#39;t obvious - there has been a big rise in malware that uses your computer to &amp;#39;mine&amp;#39; for cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin. Your bandwidth, computer power and electricity are valuable!&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" panelWidth="Medium" home="true" back="true" next="false"><nestedPage linkID="PG1535099728499" name="How does malware get on my computer?" text="&lt;p&gt;The most common ways are:&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Visiting a malicious web site which can silently install the malware,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Following a link in an email which could run a script or direct you to a malicious web site,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Clicking a pop-up on a web site,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Attaching an infected or malicious USB device,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Being connected to a network where there is an infected computer,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Giving access to someone to your computer physically or through remote access.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" align="Top"/><nestedPage linkID="PG1535099774170" name="How can I stop it?" text="&lt;p&gt;Avoiding the main ways that malware&amp;nbsp;is installed is the obvious solution, but this isn&amp;#39;t always easy.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Installing (and keeping up to date) anti-virus and anti-malware applications can help, as can applications that warn you about suspicious web sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Be sure of the identity of anyone you give access to your computer, especially if they contacted you in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Probably the most effective solution is to never follow links from an email or at least hovering over the link to check that the web address appears to be valid.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;But it is very likely that you will be affected at some point so keep your valuable files backed up and away from your computer. There are many cloud services to choose from that can keep your computer files synchonised with the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" align="Top"/><nestedPage linkID="PG1535099794270" name="What can I do if my computer is affected?" text="&lt;p&gt;Disconnect from the Internet or your network as soon as possible to avoid spreading the problem and denying access to your computer by an attacker.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Restore your operating system to an earlier date - if that fails, re-install your operating system.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;You do store your important files away from your computer, don&amp;#39;t you?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" align="Top"/></tabNav><columnPage linkID="PG1504701174800" name="They got free WiFi :-)" home="true" back="true" next="false"><nestedPage linkID="PG1504701231539" name="Free can be dangerous" text="&lt;p&gt;Free wifi hotspots can be dangerous!&#10;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;lsquo;Man in the middle&amp;rsquo; can capture all your activity and/or change your destination&#10;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;  &lt;li&gt;Use only secure access points&lt;/li&gt;&#10;  &lt;li&gt;Use Virtual Private Networking (VPN) - Windscribe, Touch VPN are free&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;&#10;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;man in the middle&quot;  src=&quot;FileLocation + 'media/vpn.jpg'&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&#10;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#10;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" align="Top"/><nestedPage linkID="PG1504701468706" name="Beware the man in the middle" text="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;FileLocation + 'media/maninmiddle.jpg'&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" align="Top"/></columnPage><mcq linkID="PG1504702024932" name="How safe are you on public WiFi?" instruction="Enter Instruction" prompt="&lt;p&gt;How can you defeat &amp;quot;the man in the middle&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" type="Multiple Answer" align="Left" panelWidth="Full" feedbackLabel="Feedback" singleRight="Your answer is correct!" singleWrong="Your answer is incorrect" multiRight="You have selected all the correct answers" multiWrong="You have not selected the correct combination of answers" checkBtnTxt="Check" trackingWeight="1.0"><option linkID="PG1504702120205" name="A" text="&lt;p&gt;Avoid free wifi hotspots&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" feedback="&lt;p&gt;This works, but sometimes there may be no alternative&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="true"/><option linkID="PG1504702186100" name="B" text="&lt;p&gt;Use a fake email to register&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" feedback="&lt;p&gt;While this might protect your identity it can&amp;#39;t stop your data being intercepted&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1504702267930" name="C" text="&lt;p&gt;Use a VPN service&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Yes - but only use a reputable provider&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="true"/></mcq><timeline linkID="PG1535119042137" name="Match the problem with the solution" text="&lt;p&gt;Can you identify the &amp;#39;cure&amp;#39; for these common problems?&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" interactivity="Matching Pairs" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Good job!&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" checkBtnTxt="Check Answers" allWrong="You have not placed any labels correctly. Try again." allWrongTracking="You have not placed any labels correctly." score="You have scored {i} out of {n}. Try again." scoreTracking="You have scored {i} out of {n}." incomplete="Complete the exercise." trackingWeight="1.0"><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119099910" name="Malware infection" text="&lt;p&gt;Keep important files backed up&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119168859" name="Trolling" text="&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t respond&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119196367" name="Being asked for personal information" text="&lt;p&gt;Find out &lt;strong&gt;who &lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;strong&gt;why&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119249014" name="Posting a public image online" text="&lt;p&gt;Keep it tightly cropped so nothing can be added&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119372063" name="Access to your mobile device" text="&lt;p&gt;Always use a passcode or biometric lock&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119430399" name="Defeating spyware" text="&lt;p&gt;Covering webcams when not in use&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119505762" name="Oversharing by mistake" text="&lt;p&gt;Checking that privacy settings are correct&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/><timelinedate linkID="PG1535119594387" name="Sharing your payment card details" text="&lt;p&gt;Check for the green padlock&lt;/p&gt;&#10;"/></timeline><gapFill linkID="PG1535120698137" name="What makes for a good password?" text="" passage="&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Hard for a |hacker| to guess&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Slow for a computer to attack by |brute force|&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Easy to |remember|&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#9;&lt;li&gt;Easy to |associate| with the site you are trying to access&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The strongest passwords use a mixture of |letters|, |numbers |and other characters.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;|Long|&amp;nbsp;passwords are better and can be remembered by using a |phrase|, song |lyrics| or a mental |image|.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" interactivity="Drag Drop" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Excellent work!&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" panelWidth="Full" checkBtn="Check" showBtn="Show Answers" gapFillWrong="You have not filled in any answers correctly. Please try again." gapFillWrongTracking="You have not filled in any answers correctly." gapFillIncomplete="Please complete the exercise." gapFillPartWrongTracking="Your correct answers are shown in green." gapFillPartWrong="Your correct answers are shown in green. Try again with those you have got wrong." trackingWeight="1.0"/><quiz linkID="PG1535122128857" name="Know your social media" order="random" numQuestions="*" align="left" panelWidth="Medium" instructions="&lt;p&gt;Find the correct answers to these social media questions&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" judge="true" showfeedback="true" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Well done!&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" quesCount="Question {i} of {n}" feedbackLabel="Feedback" singleRight="Your answer is correct!" singleWrong="Your answer is incorrect" multiRight="You have selected all the correct answers" multiWrong="You have not selected the correct combination of answers" onCompletion="You have completed the exercise" score="You scored {i} / {n}" submitBtnText="Submit" nextBtnText="Next" restartBtnText="Restart"><question linkID="PG1535122180139" prompt="&lt;p&gt;Which social media app will tell you if your post has been screen shotted?&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Q1" type="Single Answer"><option linkID="PG1535122223755" text="&lt;p&gt;Snapchat&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Snapchat" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Correct&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="true"/><option linkID="PG1535122258669" text="&lt;p&gt;WhatsApp&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="WhatsApp" feedback="" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1535122281348" text="&lt;p&gt;Facebook&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Facebook" feedback="" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1535122291436" text="&lt;p&gt;Uber&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Uber" feedback="" correct="false"/></question><question linkID="PG1535122310464" prompt="&lt;p&gt;Which of these apps &lt;strong&gt;could not&lt;/strong&gt; be considered social media?&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Q2" type="Single Answer"><option linkID="PG1535122466301" text="&lt;p&gt;Fortnite&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Fortnite" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Yes, because you can chat with others&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1535122492305" text="&lt;p&gt;Feedly&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Feedly" feedback="&lt;p&gt;Feedly is used to collect and share news feeds&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="true"/><option linkID="PG1535122591899" text="&lt;p&gt;YouTube&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="YouTube" feedback="&lt;p&gt;The comments section makes this a social app&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1535122640717" text="&lt;p&gt;Instagram&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Instagram" feedback="" correct="false"/></question><question linkID="PG1535122787446" prompt="&lt;p&gt;Which of these options &lt;strong&gt;is not&lt;/strong&gt; a good strategy if you are trolled?&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Q3" type="Single Answer"><option linkID="PG1535122843980" text="&lt;p&gt;Block the offender and un-friend them&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Block " feedback="" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1535122876728" text="&lt;p&gt;Make it clear in your reply that you have been upset&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Reply" feedback="&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s always better not to reply. You are feeding the troll if you do.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="true"/><option linkID="PG1535122961995" text="&lt;p&gt;Report problems promptly to the social network or mobile phone operator&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Report" feedback="" correct="false"/><option linkID="PG1535123027320" text="&lt;p&gt;Keep the offending&amp;nbsp;post/message&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" name="Keep " feedback="&lt;p&gt;If it upsets you&amp;nbsp;and you have to delete it, take a photo of it if you can&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" correct="false"/></question></quiz><text linkID="PG1535014596367" name="Credits &amp;amp; Copyright"><![CDATA[<div class="page-wrap">
<p style="text-align:center"><img alt="Bletchley Park Mansion" height="266" src="FileLocation + 'media/mansion-400.jpg'" width="400" /></p>

<p>Thank you for completing the Staying Safe Online module and we hope you enjoyed it and learned something from it. If you have any comments or feedback please let us know at <a href="mailto:outreach@bletchleypark.org.uk?subject=Staying%20Safe%20Online%20module" target="_blank">outreach@bletchleypark.org.uk</a></p>
</div>

<div class="site-footer"><a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" rel="license"><img alt="Creative Commons License" src="https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-nc/4.0/88x31.png" style="border-width:0" /></a><br />
This work by <a href="https://www.bletchleypark.org.uk" property="cc:attributionName" rel="cc:attributionURL" xmlns:cc="http://creativecommons.org/ns#">Bletchley Park Trust</a> is licensed under a <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" rel="license">Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License</a>.</div>
]]></text></learningObject>
